<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="95437" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Region Flag Icons" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Replaces Digraph and Map icons for Regions or Region packs with a Flag" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
# [Region Flag Icons](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/95437/Windows)
Use Flags instead of digraphs ("DE", "FR", "UK", "EE", "CN") or a map (NA) for regions and region packs.

The Theme Icons are replaced with a country's flag, which have been simplified slightly to match the vanilla themes.
The Asset Pack icons are baked on - the flag is pasted over the top of the original thumbnails.

*Icons generated by Irasponsible (aka Stelith) - Mod packaging and publishing by Konsi (aka Mimonsi)*

This mod includes icons for all currently released region packs (as of 2025/02/10). Flags are ready to go for the other content packs once they're released as well.  The plan is to use New England or Chicago for the US Northeast Pack, and Arizona or California for US Southwest - but we'll wait and see where the buildings pull their inspiration from.

**Can you move the flag to the left to match the vanilla Region icons?**
We'd love to - but we don't have a copy of the thumbnails without the stamp already on them. If you have SVG or versions of these thumbnails, hit us up!

**Why is all of North America represented with just the US Flag?**
You can choose between a United States or Canadian flag in the mod options panel.

**Why is all of Eastern Europe represented with just the Ukrainian Flag?**
Based on the Development Diary for the Eastern Europe region pack, we've gone with a Ukrainian flag to represent the region.
Signature Buildings with a specified origin have been given with a flag that identifies the country they are from. We might do this for service buildings in the pack too - it'll be a little bit more work, but figured we get the pack out sooner than later, and come back to it another time. (I'm quite busy IRL at the moment, so this might take a bit -irasponsible)

**Why is all of China represented with just the Flag of the People's Republic of China?**
The architecture shown in the content pack does not seem particularly inspired by Hong Kong nor Taiwan.

**What about the San Francisco DLC?**
I tried, but for some reason it just wouldn't work. Ah well - it means I've got the California flag ready to go if it's a good fit for the US Southwest pack.

**Why don't the zone icons have the same style as the new vanilla zone icons?**
Since the French, German, British, and Japanese packs were released before the vanilla zone icon style changed, they still use the old-style zone icons, which is the same with or without this mod. We're waiting on an update for Paradox on these ones.

**Will you add** ***x*** **?**
Plan is to add all the official region packs, and then after that - not sure.

*As a final note - flags are political symbols by their very nature. If you don't like our choice for one pack or another, you can remove the corresponding folder in the mod files, or download the files from Github and install your preferred options by placing them in your AIL Custom Thumbnails folder.*
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image1.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image3.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image4.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/region-flag-icons.1718385/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.3.2" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="79634" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
- Fix issue of flags not loading properly
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/irasponsible/cities2-flag-icons" />
</Publish>
