<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="95437" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Region Flag Icons" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Replaces the Digraph and Map icons for Regions and Region packs with a Flag icon." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
Use Flags instead of digraphs ("DE", "FR", "UK") or a map (NA) for regions and region packs.

The Theme Icons are replaced with a country's flag, which have been simplified a bit where needed.
The Asset Pack icons are baked on - so the flag is pasted over the top of the originals.

*Icons generated by Irasponsible - Mod packaging and publishing by Konsi*

Currently, this has icons for the French, German, UK, and Japan packs. Flags are ready to go for the other content packs once they're released as well.  
I'm intending to use New England or Chicago for the US Northeast Pack, Arizona or Califoria for US Southwest, and Poland or Ukraine for Eastern Europe, but we'll wait and see where the buildings pull their inspiration from.
		
**Can you move the flag to the left to match the vanilla Region icons?**
I'd love to - but I don't have a copy of the thumbnails without the stamp already on them.

**Why is all of North America represented with just the US Flag?**
A Canadian alternative is included in the games files - just rename it to match the other one and it should work after a game restart. We're considering adding a 'switch' for that one, since there's only one file to change for the NA region icon.

**What about the San Fransisco DLC?**
I tried, but for some reason it just wouldn't work. Ah well - it means I've got the California flag ready to go if it's a good fit for the US Southwest pack.

**Will you add** ***x*** **?**
Plan is to add all the official region packs, and then after that - not sure.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image1.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image3.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/image4.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/region-flag-icons.1718385/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="79634" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="" />
	<!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/irasponsible/cities2-flag-icons" />
</Publish>
